Top 5 richest NBA players in history today
The Finals NBA players who will never go Bank
Number 5
Shaquille O'Neal Shaq
History
He joined the Los Angeles Lakers at the same time is Kobe in 1996 and became the okay group
According to Investopedia
Seven hundred million dollars
Shottas on 290
In NBA history
Shaq salary
The pyramid
Aftershock retired he doubled his net worth
Chat now has a net worth of 700 million
Shaq has endorsed more than 50 products in Toto
And invested in multiple startup companies
Successed
Despite the epidemic
Shaq's income to make 60 million US dollar
Unlike other players who went bankrupt without playing basketball
Shaq's daughter
1 million original shares of Google
Number for
Junior Bridgeman I graduated from the University of Louisville
In the 1975 NBA draft the 8th pick in the first round was selected by the Box
From 1975 to 1987 he played for the bucks
In 1997
Officially retired
On January 17th 1988
Is number 2 Jersey was retired by the Box
Achieve great success in the business world
Most of his career was just a substitute
Did you plan so he has not much money in his 12-year career
It also left him unable to start enjoying life directly after retirement from the NBA
But continue to devote himself to other industry
While playing
He actually started to run business on the side
About time he had a commercial cooperation with Wendy's Burger
WeChat
Off to the end of his career he also set up a catering industry
Prepare to build a catering
His first investment Target was Wendy's Burger
Which he wants
At that time Wendy's bug is we are still in
When he started investing
In addition to Wendy's Burger
American restaurant Chili's
After the first two Investments
Successful product line
Cocola
Number 3 LeBron James LeBron is one of the highest-paid players in NBA history
His net worth has reached 480 million US dollars
According to fold 2020
People in the world
Ranked fifth among the world's highest paid athletes in 2020
LeBron signed a series of advertising endorsement
The Brand C induced include McDonald's Microsoft
State Farm
Coca-Cola
Dunkin Donuts
Baskin Robbins
According to statistics
Accounting advertising expense
James income has reached 65 million US dollars
18 million US dollars
And the annual income is about 153 million US dollars
If he retires at Fulton
Is total assets the likely to reach 1.245 billion US dollars
Number two
Magic Johnson
Castro out his career
NBA championship
According to Media statistics
Is tarek net worth has reached 600 million US dollars
Magic was once recognized as the president of the light is operation
As the greatest player in the history of the Lakers
Many Industries
From business to entertainment
Chicken travel
Johnson's income after retirement
The media wants to Strike Team
This is his nature
He should be a businessman by Nature
Number one
Michael Jordan Michael
Sneakers Air Jordan 100 million dollars a year in dividends
In 2006
Jordyn Woods
In 2014
In 2010 the book experience
At this time 180 million US dollars
Is to buy 65 shares of
The Hornets market value now exceeds 1.5 billion dollars